{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Nguyen",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "Paul Nguyen was born in Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9362186193466187,
            "question": "Is Paul Nguyen from Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8984195590019226,
            "question": "Where was Paul Nguyen born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580770611763,
            "question": "What is Paul Nguyen's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6471983790397644,
            "question": "Where did Paul Nguyen originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5994579195976257,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Paul Nguyen's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5988539457321167,
            "question": "What nationality is Paul Nguyen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5975028872489929,
            "question": "Is Canada Paul Nguyen's home country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4744410812854767,
            "question": "What country is Paul Nguyen associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.372345507144928,
            "question": "In which country did Paul Nguyen come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31717631220817566,
            "question": "To what nation does Paul Nguyen belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Nguyen was born in Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1747_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Paul Nguyen come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1747_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Paul Nguyen associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1747_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Canada Paul Nguyen's home country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1747_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1747_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because none of the provided documents support the statement that Paul Nguyen was born in Canada. In fact, one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1747/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt) explicitly states that Paul Nguyen was born in Vietnam and emigrated to France."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that Paul Nguyen was born in Vietnam and immigrated to Canada with his parents. There is no information suggesting he was born in Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Paul Nguyen was born in Vietnam.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from multiple sources indicates Paul Nguyen was born in Vietnam or France.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The multiple sources state that Paul Nguyen was born in Vietnam (1, 3, 4, 6).",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Paul Nguyen was born in Vietnam and immigrated to Canada as a refugee with his parents in 1979, not in Canada.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}